你看到我从天上飞过
You see me soaring through the sky
我看到你从地上走过
I see you below as you walk on by
我只要十秒就能清光云层
I could clear the sky in 10 seconds flat
厉不厉害
Well, how about that,
厉不厉害？
well, how about that?
我可以坐在云上好好放松
I could be sitting here on a cloud,
看著太阳缓缓下山
watching the sun as it starts to go down
现在只缺一个人
The only thing missing
那就是你
is you by my side
给我来些自信心
Give me a smidge of confidence
给我来点有意义的话
Give me a speck of something that makes sense
让我来给你依靠
Give me an idea of dependency
让我来展现忠诚心
Give me a dash of loyalty
忠诚心
Loyalty
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我总是感觉不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠诚」才是我的座右铭
That's why they call me loyalty
忠诚心
Loyalty
太阳高挂，可却下了雨
The sun shines bright, yet the rain pours on
彩虹一下来一下又离开
Rainbows here one minute and then they're gone
他们让我想起了你
They remind me of me and you
你做了什么？
What did you do?
我做了什么？
What did I do?
你双眼里的决心
Determination in those eyes
他们去哪了？已经消失了吗？
Where has it gone? Has it said goodbye?
时间过得好快
A lot has happened
可是我会陪著你
but I'll stay by your side
给我来些自信心
Give me a smidge of confidence
给我来点有意义的话
Give me a speck of something that makes sense
让我来给你依靠
Give me an idea of dependency
让我来展现忠诚心
Give me a dash of loyalty
忠诚心
Loyalty
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我总是感觉不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠诚」才是我的座右铭
That's why they call me loyalty
我们在一起时间就会静止
Time stands still when you're with me
我要怎么让你看清
How can I make you see?
你的白目让我想发狂
Your crazy antics make me want to scream
吼你名字吼到喉咙烂掉
your name so loud till my throat starts to bleed
烂掉
to bleed
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
总是感觉
the feeling in my heart
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我总是感觉不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠诚」才是我的座右铭
That's why they call me loyalty
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我总是感觉不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠诚」才是－－
That's why they call--
所以「忠诚」才是我的－－
That's why they call me--
我能给你我孤单的灵魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我总是感觉不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以给我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因为你知道我会陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠诚」才是我的座右铭
That's why they call me loyalty